This hijab is really bright, Honey.  There, I
took the same length, yeah.
We shape the hijab.
There,
this is the latest hijab from Mayor Style.
The ingredients are also very different, Honey.  But
still, premium quality.  Then
I immediately put pentel, yes.  Put a safety pin.
The way to write it is like this, Say.
First we put the left and
right sides together.  Then we stick the safety pin in
until it goes through.  Then fold it like
this.  Then we stab the orange
twice again.  That's more or less
like that, yeah.  Pull it up like
this, Guys.  One was taken to the
back.  I folded the other one like
this.
Then put a safety pin on
the back and put it down and tidy it up
.